good job kentucky! 
title should be: "lady who refused to do job, loses job."
from what i remember, this awful bitch owes the people of kentucky some goddamn money... and human beings, in general, an apology
guess it was god's will ¯\\\_(ツ)\_/¯
good, now she can go back to husband number, what was it, four?
700 votes. remember every vote matters.
it appears that an all powerful god rejected her.
thoughts and prayers.
i am thrilled that this relic is being relegated to the dung heap of history.
you just *know* this... woman? is going to play the shit out of being a victim on conservative social media. she's going to claim that she was voted out by fraudulent schemes that rigged the system because she was a christian and the satan-worshiping liberal soy-boy sissies hacked the machines to get her removed.

no, bitch. you lost because you're not fit to do a simple job. you are *unqualified* for the position you formerly filled. all you had to do was sign legal documentation that two individuals had entered into a consensual marriage under the guidelines of state legislation so their union would be recognized by the court. you didn't do that. you lost your job.

if you don't like that gay couples are getting married **then get a different job**.
won't shake the hand of our ally, yet:

> “this is code-word information,” said a u.s. official familiar with the matter, using terminology that refers to one of the highest classification levels used by american spy agencies. **trump “revealed more information to the russian ambassador than we have shared with our own allies.”**

-

> **trump went on to discuss aspects of the threat that the united states only learned through the espionage capabilities of a key partner.** [...] most alarmingly, officials said, trump revealed the city in the islamic state’s territory where the u.s. intelligence partner detected the threat.

-

> u.s. officials said that the national security council continues to prepare multi-page briefings for trump to guide him through conversations with foreign leaders **but that he has insisted that the guidance be distilled to a single page of bullet points, and often ignores those.**

-

> **“i’m sure kislyak was able to fire off a good cable back to the kremlin with all the details” he gleaned from trump**, said the former u.s. official who handled intelligence on russia.
this news in 1997: holy shit!

this news in 2002: world war is coming. 

this news in 2012: potus is killing america. 

this news in 2017: i guess it's monday. 
>in his meeting with lavrov, trump seemed to be boasting about his inside knowledge of the looming threat. “i get great intel. i have people brief me on great intel every day,” trump said, according to an official with knowledge of the exchange.

what the fuck!  you're the fucking president, of course you get great intel.  what a fucking moron.
> crooked hillary clinton and her team "were extremely careless in their handling of very sensitive, highly classified information." not fit!

https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/750648675186147328
>trump “revealed more information to the russian ambassador than we have shared with our own allies.”
i'm starting to think we live in a simulation specifically designed to be sean spicer's​ personal hell. 
>“it is all kind of shocking,” said a former senior u.s. official close to current administration officials. “**trump seems to be very reckless, and doesn’t grasp the gravity of the things he’s dealing with, especially when it comes to intelligence and national security. and it’s all clouded because of this problem he has with russia**.”

no shit! this is what everyone's been saying!

edit: [apparently buzzfeed is saying they have sources telling them it's worse than what's even being reported by the wp.](https://www.buzzfeed.com/jimdalrympleii/trump-highly-classified-information-russians?utm_term=.cwmbxb4xz#.mldapawpe)

>two us officials who were briefed on trump’s disclosures last week confirmed to buzzfeed news the veracity of the post report, with one official noting that “it’s far worse than what has already been reported.”
[reuters has confirmed independently](https://twitter.com/reuters/status/864249402571010049)

edit: has also been confirmed by [nyt](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/05/15/us/politics/trump-russia-classified-information-isis.html) and 
[buzzfeed](https://www.buzzfeed.com/jimdalrympleii/trump-highly-classified-information-russians)

edit2: [**wsj**](https://www.wsj.com/articles/white-house-denies-trump-gave-classified-information-to-russian-officials-1494890345) now confirming, but with only one independent source. 
this tweet aged well

>crooked hillary clinton and her team "were extremely careless in their handling of very sensitive, highly classified information." not fit!

https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/750648675186147328
guys, help.

i'm full-on addicted to american politics and i'm not even from your country. wapo might as well be crack with a subscription service. 
